morning catastrophe control President Obama sent the heart of the nation about the economy
早上灾难控制总统奥巴马发出的国家的心脏有关经济
America
美国
what is Congress going to approve a plan that even the president called imperfect
什么是国会将批准一项计划，连总统被称为不完全
Chris Brown
克里斯·布朗
food stamps even though she is not getting paid today Tuesday February 10th
即使她没有得到报酬今天周二2月10日粮票
NBC News
NBC新闻
good morning the hard sell President Obama head of the Capitol Hill tonight to deliver what could be a make or break speech on healthcare reform preview from White House press secretary Robert Gibbs
早上好强买强卖奥巴马总统头上的国会山今晚提供什么可能是成败的讲话从白宫新闻秘书罗伯特·吉布斯医疗改革预览
grizzly find the pickle say that bone fragment kidnapper Phillip Garrido came from a human this is NBC News obtains chilling music and more than 30 years ago
灰熊找到咸菜说，骨头碎片绑架者菲利普·加里多是来自一个人，这是NBC新闻获得令人不寒而栗的音乐和超过30年前
do the lyrics for section with young girls
做歌词的年轻女生节
Rafael Nadal finals today Wednesday September 9
纳达尔决赛今天周三9月9日
good morning welcome to today on a Wednesday morning
早上好，欢迎大家出席今天的周三上午
what the president has made today
什么总统今天发表
people are saying that his approval ratings are sliding critics of its healthcare overhaul Argo so the president will try to quiet down by laying out
人们说，他的支持率正在滑动的医疗改革阿尔戈的批评使总统将尝试通过铺设安静下来
good morning view from inside rheumatic new images of rescue researching the interior fuse for the cruise liner Natalie and divas last the whole the side of the ship to look for possible survivors on the captain make his first appearance in court
从里面抢救研究的邮轮Natalie和提婆持续整个船舷寻找的队长可能的生还者，对在法庭他的首次出现内部保险丝风湿性新的图像早上好景色
why did he today Tuesday January 17 2012
他为什么今天星期二2012年1月17日
today
今天
curry live from Studio 1a Rockefeller Plaza
从工作室1A洛克菲勒广场咖喱直播
and welcome to the jam this Tuesday morning on in car
并欢迎卡纸本周二早上在车
rescue crews back at work inside that crippled cruise liner this morning after they were forced to suspend their search for survivors because of bad weather on Monday
救援人员回到那个残缺的邮轮内部工作今天上午，他们被迫因恶劣天气后暂停其搜寻幸存者周一